msfn.org 2012-09-20

# privacy policy for msfn.org

**MSFN Privacy Policy**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at xper at msfn.org. At [www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/), the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by [www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/) and how it is used.

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, [www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/) makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

[www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/) does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense and VibrantMedia. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on [www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/) send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

[www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org/) has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. [www.msfn.org](http://www.msfn.org%27s/) privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites.

MSFN has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website. MSFN is not affiliated in any way with Microsoft. 

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our web site. Your IP address is not used to identify you. However, all posts in our forums and comments to articles have an associated IP address recorded. This IP address is never shown to other users and it is only collected in order to help us to prevent unsolicited posting to our forums (spam). 

All users have their user name, country and date of inclusion listed in our User List. This list is only visible to other registered users. The e-mail icon allows users to send private messages between them, but neither the sender's or recipient's e-mail addresses are disclosed. If the user requires privacy, an option is available on My Profile to hide the user name from this list. 

Our site uses cookies to keep track of your login. Cookies are simple data files that store information. We do not install any program on your computer while visiting our site. The information stored in the cookie file is used to store the login information if the user decides to use our auto login feature. 

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and e-mail address) and optional demographic information (like city and country). If the user opts in, we use the contact information (e-mail address) from the registration form to send any important information regarding its registration with MSFN. 

This site contains links to other sites. MSFN is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

By using this site you agree that you undertake any guides, instructions, advice and implement it at your own risk. However where possible we strive to ensure that information is complete, acurate and practical. 

MSFN cannot be held liable for any damage to physical or intellectual property. MSFN is not responsible for posts, comments or views of our members. All posts and comments remain the copyright of the posters. MSFN reserves the right to edit, delete or move posts made on this site. MSFN reserves the right to keep members posts and not delete those from forums. A copy of Forum rules can be viewed [here](http://www.msfn.org/board/index.php?app=forums&module=extras&section=boardrules).
